《越狱》前情回顾
previously on prison break
金曼先生
Mr.Kim
唐克雷蒂 莎拉  我正在处理
Sara Tancredi. I'm on it.
你就花了你所有的时间去追查她?
Is pursuing her the best use of your time?
我会告诉总统的
I'll let the president know.
我会直接和总统联系
I contact the president directly.
我来联系她
I'll contact her.
帕托塞克 没有家人? 什么都没?
No family with patoshik?Nothing?
是的
Yeah.
因为四年前 他把他们都杀了
Until about four years ago when he killed them all.
费尔南多 苏克雷 2点左右 在拉斯维加斯出现
Fernando Sucre-- he was in las vegas around 2:00.
往西边去了 就像巴格威尔和富兰克林
Out west,  just-just like Bagwell and Franklin.
你知道 D.B. 库珀吗?
You know D.B. Cooper?
他的钱藏在了犹他
The money's in Utah,
他们都要去那里拿钱
and they're all going to get it.
你是其中的一个 福克斯河 的逃犯
You're one of them Fox River boys.
哦
快点  你找到地图了吗?
Come on.You got the map?
没有  让人捷足先登了
No.   Somee else does.
在我毁掉他之前
Before I destroyed it,
我已经记在我脑子里了
I committed it to my photographic memory.
我提供信息
I have the information,
而你们就负责
you have the manual requirements necessary
挖出韦斯特莫兰德的赃款
to unearth westmoreland's buried booty.
- 进去  - 好的
- Get in. - Okay.
就在前面了
Should be dead ahead.
上面重新建造过了
The bastards built over it.
完了
It's gone.
我们还有15分钟就要开门了
we have to open up in 15 minutes.
那不要紧
So, it doesn't matter.
快来吧 我说过了  不
I dare you.I said...I said no.
快来吧  求你了
I dare you.Please?
那个农场没了  迈克尔
The ranch is gone, Michael.
是的  五百万可能还在
Well, the five million might not be.
那你打算怎么找那些钱
And you gonna find it how?
难道你纹了个探测器在你屁股上?
What, you got a divining rod tattooed on your ass?
我不想听从你嘴里
I don't want to hear
说出的任何话
anything out of your mouth
除了你对地图的记忆，也把地图上的东西都给我说出来
other than what your photographic memory spits out regarding that map.
你要注意你和我说话的语气  小子
You watch your tone with me, boy.
我只会看着你被扔到
I will watch you get tossed
马路上自生自灭  小子
to the side of the road to fend for yourself, boy.
因为如果你想不起来那个地窖在哪
Because if you can't remember where that silo was,
你对我们来说就是个废物
you're worthless to us.
嗨  让我出去!
Yo, let me out!
闭嘴!
Shut up!
地图!
The map!
哦  哦  好
Uh, uh, okay.
好  好  好的
Okay, okay, all right, all right, all right
那个农场... 那个农场
the ranch...the ranch was
在一个方形区域当中  一边是雪普路
the ranch was in the center of a box--sheep road on one side,
和可可辛路垂直交叉
kokosing road perpendicular.
藏钱地的中心点
In the center of the property
就是农场的房子
was the ranch house.
房子的四周都是树
And the ranch house was surrounded by trees.
这些树最多只种了一年
Every tree here is a year old at most.
除了那些
Except those.
地窖在哪?
Where is the silo?
在...在树林里面
In...side the trees.
我想可能是靠左边
I want to say on the left,
但是  那应该有个谷仓啊
but that m have been a barn.
我把能记住的都说了  伙计
I remembered the best I could, gents,
但是没想到这个地方
but I didn't know this place
现在盖了这么多房子在上面
would now be smothered in tract homes,
所以  你知道我也没办法 但我并不是废物
so, you know,I'm sorry that I-I'm not rainman over here.
我是马宏 你好!
Alex Mahone,How are you!
我是 莱尔 山德斯
Lyle Sands.
我们已经给所有人都下达了命令
We've been briefed on all the men at large.
盐湖城的所有部队和警力资源
The full force and resources of the entire Salt Lake city
陆军校级军官都听从您的指挥
field officer are at your disposal.
谢谢  我需要的那些文件弄到了吗
Thank you.Do you have those files my office requested
关于D.B. 库珀那个案子的
on the D.B. Cooper case?
我们正在提取
We're pulling them now.
- 就是那个30年前D.B. 库珀的案子吗? - 是的
- And this is the D.B. Cooper case from 30 years ago?- Correct.
如果我能立即拿到那些文件
If I can get those files immediately,
我会很感谢
I'd appreciate it.
嗨  对不起  但我想问一下
Hey, sorry, but I have to ask.
你不是为了福克斯河的八个逃犯来的吗?
Aren't you here for the Fox River eight?
是的  而且他们就在犹他州
I am, and they're here in Utah
为了D.B. 库珀的钱  那些文件怎么样了  莱尔?
to get D.B.Cooper's money,so how abouthose files, Lyle?
地窖
Silo.
地窖  地窖  地窖  地窖
Silo, silo, silo, silo.
真是太蠢了
This is stupid.
我们要把这个地方找出来
We're going to get made out here.
啊  闭嘴  我想我记起来了
Ah, shut it.I think I remember.
如果打赌的话  我敢很确定
If I had to bet, I'd lay
地窖就在那个平房的左侧
it all on the silo being on the left of the ranch house
在树林里面
inside the trees.
不  是在树林外
No.It's outside the trees.
在那
Right there.
看见那两棵树了吗?
You see those two trees?
它们比其他的都矮
They're shorter than the rest.
它们都是在同一个时间种下的
They were all planted at the same time,
但是那两棵树没有得到充足的阳光
but those two didn't get as much sunlight.
有东西挡着它们
Something was in their way.
地窖
The silo.
我们的钱应该就在那间车库下面
Our money should be right there under that garage.
你最好没猜错  小子
You better be right, boy.
这不是一个重要的小镇
This isn't a high-end subdivision.
他们马马虎虎很快造好了这个地方
They slapped this place up overnight.
地窖的地基有可能还在那
The silo's foundation might still be there.
为了省钱  他们可能就用混凝土
To save money, they probably just laid the concrete
浇铸车库的地面就在地窖的上面
for the garage floor right on top of it.
我们只要一直往下挖
We'll dig straight down.
如果我们碰到地基的话就留下
If we hit the foundation, we stay.
如果没有  我们就走人
But if not, we go.
现在就开始吧
Let's do it.
哦  妈的
Oh, man.
哦  哦
没问题  用把螺丝刀
Ain't no problem that a screwdriver
在她太阳穴上开个洞就搞定了
to her temple won't fix.
人总有一死  小子
people die all the time, boys.
但五百万这一辈子可只有这一次
Five million dollars comes once in a lifetime.
让我出去!
Let me out!
好的  我们要做点什么
Well, we got to do something
这次不要伤害任何人
and it's not going to involve hurting anyone.
我有个主意
I got an idea.
首先  我们需要一些装备
First, we're going to need some supplies.
110%不同意
110% do not agree with this.
每个人为了拿到钱都会竭尽全力
Everybody's got to pitch in to make this happen.
但在监狱里
But back in the big house,
那小子就被证实他不可靠
the boy proved he couldn't be trusted.
所以我们才开车到这个地方
Which is why we're doing it here.
如果他在镇上被捕
If he gets caught in town,
他不会知道房子的具体位置
he ain't got a clue where the house is.
另外  我们也不完全相信你
Besides, you're the one we can't turn our backs on.
哦
你知道吗   我在里面可能会憋死  老兄
You know, I could have died in there, man.
嗯  你猜怎么着?
Well, guess what?
我们需要你去做些事情
We need you to do something.
我需要你为我做些事
I need you to do something for me.
我想得到我那部分钱
I want my cut of the money.
好的   等你证明我们可以相信你我们再谈
Well, we'll talk once you prove we can trust you.
我去做什么
What do I got to do?
回那个花卉店把这单字上写的东西拿来
I want you to go back to that garden center and get everything on this list.
然后把车加满油
Then gas up the car.
我们一个小时后在这里见面
And we'll meet you right back here in an hour.
好的
All right.
还有  大卫...
And David...
别把这事搞砸了
don't screw this up.
这里不再是福克斯河了  老兄
This ain't Fox River no more, man.
这次才是真正的交易
You're looking at the real deal now.
但我要我那部分钱
But I want my cut.
一小时后我会回来的
I'll be back in an hour.
我们走
Let's go.
错误
Mistake.
严重的错误
Big mistake.
看到你真高兴啊
am I glad to see you.
你走到这的?
Did you walk here?
哦 不... 是...
Well, no...it's...
说来话长啊  伙计
it's-it's just a long story, man.
还以为你和你家人在一起了呢
Thought you were meeting up with your family.
我碰到了... 碰到了点麻烦
I met a...I met a few roadblocks.
你呢?
You?
是的
Yeah.
让我猜猜看... 你打算去图勒镇?
Let me guess...you're going to Tooele.
是的
Yep.
我们似乎都往同一个地方去啊
it looks like we're going in the same direction.
希望不会太迟
Hopefully we're not too late.
能搭个车吗?
Can I hitch a ride?
嘿...
Hey...
我会让你觉得是值得的
I'll make it worth your while.
有好消息  长官
Got some good news, sir.
在第一时间发现了帕托塞克
Got our first tip on patoshik.
在威斯康星州思达 格鲁夫的一家快餐店
Spotted at a burger joint in cedar grove, Wisconsin.
马上交给当地警方办吧
Just hand it over to local authorities for now.
我们今天就处理犹他州的事
The only thing we're working today is Utah
还有D.B. 库珀这事
and D.B. Cooper.
明白了
Got it.
莱尔
Lyle.
在这个单子上有个人
Therers a guy here listed
是我们找到唯一一个 收到过D.B. 库珀的钱的人哈罗德 詹金斯
as having the only D.B. Cooper bill ever found in circulation, Harold Jenkins.
是的 D.B.库珀从詹金斯那里买过汽油
Yeah, D.B. Bought gas from jenkins
在劫机那天用百元大钞买的
with a hundred on the day of the hijacking.
我们查过了序列号
We checked the serial numbers
是吻合的
and they matched.
你是负责这案子的?
You worked the case?
新人刚毕业时
Fresh out of the academy.
一直都没人能弄清楚这事
And nobody's cracked it yet.
为什么你认为
What makes you think
那些逃犯知道钱在哪?
that these escapees know where the money is?
因为他们很可能是和
Because they may have been
真正的D.B. 库珀关在一起的
locked up with the real D.B. Cooper.
这个加油站的詹金斯
This Jenkins from the gas station,
- 还活着么?  - 应该是的
- he still alive?- Should be.
那时他只有18岁
He was only 18 at the time.
我们过去见见他
Let's go say hi to him.
对不起  你所拨的电话号码不完整
we're sorry.Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
请核对您的号码后重新拨打
Please check the number and dial again.
有关于唐克雷蒂 莎拉的新情况了?
Do you have updates on Sara Tancredi?
我想这是你来这的原因吧?
I'm assuming why you're here
呃  是的
Yes, um,
斯科菲尔德给她寄了邮件留了信息
Scofield sent her a message through the mail
可那个电话号码打不通
that phone number that was disconnected.
你知道  说实话
You know, to be honest,
我想和总统做个简报
I was expecting to brief the president.
呃  关于这个...
Yeah, about that,
现在  你也知道  凯若琳非常忙
right now,as you can imagine, Caroline's quite busy.
她一直都很忙
She's always been busy.
我和她共事了15年
I've been working side-by-side with her for 15 years.
保罗  她现在是美国总统了
Paul, she's the President of the United States now.
是的  比尔  我帮她坐上这个位子
Yes, Bill, and I helped put her there.
如果你还想她继续做下去
if you'd like for her to remain in office,
你最好接受我的建议
you'll take my advice
从现在开始离她远点
and just stay on the sidelines for now.
她必须完全隔绝
She needs to be completely insulated
任何和与林肯 布伦斯有关的事情
from anything regarding Lincoln Burrows
我想和她谈谈
I want to talk to her.
你现在只向我汇报  只有我
You report to me now, and only me.
没有我的允许
without my approval,
你不用再联系凯若琳
You're not to try and contact Caroline again
未经通知你也不要在这出现
and you don't show up here unannounced.
完成你的工作  抓到布伦斯
Finish the job you were given; get Burrows.
如果你要说通过唐克雷蒂 莎拉可以抓到他
If you're telling me the road to him leads through Sara Tancredi,
那就想尽一切办法去追查
by all means, pursue it.
一旦这事完成了
And once that's been accomplished
一切都结束了后
and this whole thing goes away,
那时我们会考虑让你再回到凯若琳的身边
we'll go about transitioning you back into Caroline's life.
现在还有关于莎拉的其他消息吗?
Now do you have anything else on Ssara?
总统是坚定不移地信任你
The President has unwavering faith in you.
她希望你确保能够
Wants to make sure you
通过参议院的正式批准
go through the Senate approval process with your eyes wide open.
那么我们现在要应对什么?
So what are we up against?
参议院和众议院的一些主要同盟者
Key allies in the House and Senate are
梅耶霍夫 巴恩维尔还有萨默维尔
Meyerhoff, Barnwell and Summerville.
我们要靠他们
We're counting on them
去拉拢那些中立派
to sway the middle.
那谁是我们的对手?
But who's the opposition?
议员布拉克和奇乐
Senators Blake and Killoren
他们公开表示反对你当选副总统
have openly vocalized their opposition to you as VP.
知道为什么吗?
Any indications to why?
政治上的反击吧
Political payback
因为上个月总统通过了能源法案
for the President's vote on the energy bill last month.
我们要出其不意
Took them by surprise
他们不喜欢意外
and they don't like surprises.
兰斯  这是我爸爸弗兰克
Lance, this is,my father Frank.
很高兴见到你  先生
Pleasure to meet you, sir.
没什么大不了的
It's nothing to lose sleep over.
说实话  最大的问题
Frankly, the biggest issue
是我们要集中精力对付
we have to address are
对你女儿的指控
the charges facing your daughter.
市长  你在听我讲吗?
Governor, are you with me?
当然是
Absolutely.
别吵了 混蛋
no, just chill, dawg.
听着  我们一离开  一出城
Listen, once we ro out, we bounce out of town,
我们会留下信息 然后他们会找到你的
we'll drop a dime and they will find you.
安静点
Just be quiet.
再忍忍吧  伙计
Just chill, man.
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you!
伍迪?
Woody?
你在哪?
Where you at?
伍迪?
Woody?
我要找威廉姆斯警长
I need Sheriff Williams.
是的  我在
Yeah, I'll hold.
伍迪?
Woody?
你在哪学的电工?
When'd you learn about electricity?
我过去常常从配电箱偷铜线
I used to steal copper wiring from transformer boxes.
然后在码头那边卖掉  赚点钱
Sell 'em on the docks, make a few bucks.
当然了  那时你还在读书
When you were at school, of course.
我只是看看  帅哥
I was just looking, pretty.
有个老掉牙的笑话怎么说来着?
What's that old chestnut?
我看看菜单
I can look at the menu.
并不意味着我想吃
Doesn't mean I'm gonna eat.
我们进去  拿到钱 然后出来  仅此而已
We get in, we get the money, we get out.That's it.
那当然了
No, absolutely.
行了
We're good.
现在就看那小子的了
Now it's just up to the kid.
东西都拿齐了吗?
Did you get everything?
是的  是的  拿到了
Yeah.Yeah, I got it.
出什么事了?
What?
没事  冷静  我处理好了
Nothing.It's cool.I handled it.
出了什么事?!
What?!
好吧
Okay.
看吧是这样
Check it.
刚才有个笨蛋进了店里
This fool came in the shop.
他悄悄溜进来的
He was acting all shady.
他发现有点不对劲  所以就拿起了电话
He got a bad vibe, so he picked up his celly phone,
他开始打电话  然后我就打晕了他
he started to make a call, so I popped him.
你做了什么?!
You did what?!
我用铁铲打晕了他  伙计!
I hit him with a shovel, man!
我不知道该怎么办!
I didn't know what else to do!
然后我就把他绑了起来放在里屋
So I just, I tied him up and in put him in the back room
和另外那个乡巴佬一起
with that other country hick.
这下好了  这下好了
Here we go.Here we go.
我还是脱险了  你个变态!
I came through you gimp!
他打电话给谁了?
Who was he calling?
县治安官
The sheriff.
伙计  伙计  我真的不知道
Man, man, I-I don't know, dude.
真的事发突然...  电话有没有打通?!
It just, it set off...did the call go through?!
- 也许  伙计...  - 也许是什么意思? 到底有没有打通?!
- Maybe, man...-what do you mean, maybe?Did the call go through?!
是的  不  我不知道
Yes.No, I don't know!
我真的不知道  伙计
I don't know, man.
但我拿到了工具
but I got the gear.
我们现在得赶紧行动了
We got to move on this now.
谁啊?
yes?
很抱歉打扰你  太太
Sorry to bother you, ma'am.
你家是不是断电了?
Is your electricity out?
打扰下  我要找一个叫 哈罗德 詹金斯 的人
Excuse me.I'm looking for a Harold Jenkins.
在这
Right here.
亚历山大 马宏  联邦探员
Alexander Mahone, FBI.
我一直待在她50英尺以外
I'm staying 50 feet away from her at all times.
她该死的到底还想怎么样?
What the hell else does she want?
我来这不是为这个的
I'm not here about that.
那是为了什么?
What are you here for?
D.B. 库珀
D.B. Cooper.
大家还想要知道那家伙的事啊?
People still want to know about that guy?
真是难以置信
Unbelievable.
你以前在美国福克加油站工作的
You worked the gas station in American Fork
那个他加油的地方
where he filled up.
是的  那家伙看上去很普通
Yeah.Normal-looking guy.
没说几句话
Barely said a word.
你的陈述里有些矛盾
There were some discrepancies
你30年前填的那个
in the statement you filed 30 years ago.
在报告里  记录着
In the report, it's noted
你说他早上7点来加的油
that you said he filled up at 7:00 A.M.
但在后来你又说是晚上7点
But on another occasion,you said it was 7:00 P.M.
到底那个是真的?
Which was it?
两个都是
Both.
他加了两次油?
He gassed up twice?
是的
Yeah.
两次都是加满的?
Full tanks both times?
是的
Yeah.
为什么这么问?
Why?
一个系统什么?
A systems what?
一次系统诊断测试
It's a systems diagnostics test.
探测显示了
Footage from our gopher cam picked up　exactly
你的电线
where your line
腐烂的准确位置
was corrupted.
那是谁让它烂掉的  你们这些人吗?
And who corrupted it, you guys?
也许
Maybe.
我所知道的就是我的上级打电话来说
All I know is my supervisor called and said　he
让我和我的同事来这里
wants me and my crew to get over here
以最快的速度解决这个问题
and fix that problem double-quick, double-time.
那... 你不是电力公司的?
So...you're not with the electric company?
是的  太太
No, ma'am.
当然你也完全可以打电话给电力公司
Now feel free to call your company,
但是我要告诉你  他们会做的就是
but I should tell you, all they'll do
派来些技术人员   如果你够幸运的话或许是明天
is send over some tech,maybe tomorrow if you're lucky.
然后他会花一整天来找到问题
And he'll spend a whole day trying to find the problem
之后再花一天时间来修好它
and another day trying to fix it.
但我们现在就在这
But we're here right now
我们马上就能使你喝到冰果汁
we're ready to turn your juice back on.
果汁?
My juice?
是的
That's right.
那么  呃...
And, uh...
那是你的人?
and that's your crew?
是的  太太
Yes, ma'am.
是的 丹尼尔.库博那时开的是一辆 1965年的雪威.诺瓦（雪佛莱汽车的一种型号）
Yeah, D.B.Cooper was driving a 1965 Chevy Nova.
没有文档纪录说库博自己有车
There's no record on file that cooper even had a car.
但查尔斯.韦斯特莫兰德有
But charles westmoreland did,
他那个时候已经登记了
nd the car registered to him at the time
是一辆1965年16加仑油箱的雪威.诺瓦
was a 1965 Chevy Nova with a 16-gallon gas tank.
你知道  那个时候  这种型号的雪威
Back then, a chevy that size probably got what,
用一加仑的油能跑上8英里?
eight miles to the gallon?
现在库博开的那辆福特 正停在美国福克加油站
Now, D.B. Stopped at the station in american fork,
不久前刚加了一次油   然后当天晚上又回来
gassed up once early that day and then came back later
再加一次
that same night and gassed up again.
现在  为什么一个要去墨西哥的人
Now, why would a guy headed to Mexico,
要24小时不停地绕一个大圈
which is a straight shot south,
而不从大路直走
drive off the main road for an all-day detour?
为了那钱
The money.
对了  库博也就是韦斯特莫兰德跳下飞机时
Exactly.Cooper/westmoreland jumped out of a plane
带着500万
with $5 million.
但韦斯特莫兰德被捕的时候
when he was arrested.
并没有发现那笔钱
But westmoreland didn't have the money on him
他在被逮捕前就已经把钱给藏好了
He ditched it before he got caught.
给我那支奇异笔
Give me that magic marker.
从美国福克加油站开出   他不可能开得很远
From American Fork, he couldn't have gone　further
不可能超出64英里的范围
than 64 miles in any direction.
我要知道那个周长范围内 你得到的一切情况
I want everything you've got in that perimeter.
那些罪犯就在其中的一个镇里
Those cons are in one of these towns,
要是少了其中一个人
and if there's so much as a cat missing in one of them,
我要你马上通知我
I want to know about it.
那根出了问题的电缆就在你的车库下面
The defective cable runs right beneath your garage.
我们得挖开地板才能找到
We're gonna have to dig up the floor to get to it.
好吧  那谁来付这些钱
Well, who's gonna pay for this
还有谁来负责清洁和重修这地方呢?
and what about the cleanup and the repair?
放心吧  公司会负责这一切费用
Well, the company will cover all costs.
我们只是挖出一条小槽
We'll just dig a small trench,
等把电缆给修好了  我们会铺上水泥
once we're finished, we'll re-lay the cement.
然后看起来就跟新的一样
It'll look as good as new.
这要花多长时间啊?
How long is it going to take?
总之  我们今天会做完的
One way or another,we'll be out of here today.
我们得马上开始动工了  太太
We really need to get started, ma'am.
我们不会
We wouldn't
让像你这样一个漂亮的美人
want a pretty little thing like yourself
今晚呆在一个黑乎乎的房子里  是吧?
sitting in the dark tonight, now do we?
那得看我跟谁呆在一起了
Now that depends on who I'm sitting with.
说得对
Touche.
那好吧
fine, that's okay,
你们该做什么
and do whatever y'all need to do.
就开始吧
y'all go ahead
珍尼特  这里的噪音可能会很大
Jeanette, the noise might be substantial.
要不你可以去打打网球什么的
You mi
噢  不
Oh, no it's...
现在打太热了
it's too hot for that now.
还有  我会看着你们的
Plus, I'm gonna keep an eye on y'all
以免你们都把我家的东西给偷走了
and make sure you don't steal anything.
夫人
Ma'am.
- 你还好吧  -很好
- How are you? - Good.
好了  那小子去哪了?
All right, where's Tweener?
他在另一个门
He's next door
把那加长的电线给接上
plugging in the extension cord.
我们要把这水泥板给凿开
We're going to have to cut up the cement.
嘿  这回我们可有伴了
Yo, we gots company.
嘿  好久不见了  斯科菲尔德
What'up, snowflake?
你总是算准了来
your timing is flawless.
我可没跟踪你
I don't follow.
呃  跟你说清了吧
Well, let me try to explain it to you.
我们在这有点事要办
We're trying to run something here
而且我们不能让别人进来
and we can't have people walking in off the street.
噢  噢  好吧  你意思是想让我们走
Oh, oh, okay, so you want us to leave
然后把钱给我们寄过去?
and then you can just mail us the check?
苏克雷  我知道你相信我
Sucre, I know you trust me.
你知道我会把你该得的那部分给你的
And you know I'll cut you in on that money.
但你们两个现在在这里
But the two of you being here right
会坏这一切的
now jeopardizes everything.
我哪也不去
I'm not going nowhere.
我要我那一份钱
I want my share of the money.
嘿  等一下  等一下  伙计
Wait a minute.Hold on, man.
我们之前不是说好的吗?
Ain't we did this dance before?
我说我要加入你们
You know, I say I want in,
你说不
you say no.
然后我威胁说要把这事告诉别人
Then I threaten to tell somebody about what's going on here.
于是你就乖乖地同意了
Then you decide to play nice
我们可是和睦的一家人啊
and then we're one big, happy family.
我们不要浪费时间了  好吗?
Why don't we just stop wasting time, all right?
谢谢
Thank you.
我靠  老兄  你还活着啊?
Damn, man, you still alive?
还正准备回家呢 小子
And kickin', home boy.
你是怎么找到我们的?
How'd you find us?
老兄 要是我能把全世界的 通讯卫星都迅速部署起来给美国……
Man, if I can do rapid deployment of satellite communications for uncle sam all over the world...
你们进展得怎么样啊?
how are you guys doing?
你们是谁?
Who are you?
他们是谁?
Who are they?
呃  我刚才打电话给我的上级
I, uh, I had to call my supervisor.
他多派了两个人过来
He sent them right over.
这项任务是当务之急
This job is a top priority
我们想尽可能
we want to get this
又快又好地完成这项工作
done as quickly and efficiently as possible.
呃  珍尼特  我刚才说过了
Well, Jeanette, like I said,
这里要做的工作很多
there's a lot of work to do,
会很吵的
and it's going to be noisy.
啊  对了  要喝的吗?  我刚忘记问你们了
Oh, drinks.I forgot to ask.
不用了  谢谢
We're good.Thanks.
嘿  伙计  情况不妙啊
Yo, man, this is not good.
这样的话她会整天
We got her
进进出出  问来问去的
up in our grill checking in on us all the time.
他说得有道理
The boy is right.
你们知道我挖不了
And since I can't dig,
我自愿出去引开她的注意力
I'll volunteer to keep her occupied.
警告你  不要碰她
You don't touch her.
你以为你是谁啊  圣母玛利亚?
Who are you, sister Mary Francis?
我知道怎么做得漂亮点
I know how to play nice.
我会盯着你的
I'll be watching.
比利  是你吗?
Billy? Is that you?
呃  是的
Yep.
噢
太谢谢你了
thank you kindly.
恩  怎么你不用工作呢?
Well now, how did you get out of working?
工作规定
Union rules.
总要有个人来做监督工作的
one crew member always has to supervise.
我会时不时去看一下他们
I'll check on them in a bit.
来点柠檬水?
Lemonade?
好的
Mm.
多放点冰
more ice.
我总喜欢在自己的那份上面
加一点...喔
And I like mine with a little...oops.
但你现在在工作  我想你能...
But since you'ren the clock, I guess you can't...
和我一起喝酒吧?
join me?
就喝两个手指高好了
Just two fingers.
好长一段时间了
been a while.
恩?
Yeah?
威士忌的味道总让我
Whiskey always makes me feel...
回忆起往事
irascible.
我不明白是什么意思?
I don't know what that means.
不过我确实很喜欢你说的样子
but I do like the sound of it.
你喷了天使牌香水?
Are you wearing Angel Perfume?
是的
I am.
噢...恩...
Oh...En...
是不是让你想起了你的前女友?  我猜
that reminds you of an ex, I take it.
是的
Yeah.
那是些美好的记忆...
now, was that good memories...
还是不好的?
or bad memories?
两样都是
Both.
你和玛丽克鲁兹谈过了吗?
Did you talk to Maricruz?
我不想谈这个
I don't want to talk about it.
我要去喝点水什么的
I got to get some water or something.
去屋的另一边那有水管可以喝
Use the hose on the other side of the house.
苏克雷...
Sucre...
以后  如果你有麻烦
down the road, if you're in trouble,
上europeangoldfinch.net
europeangoldfinch.Net.
我们可以用这个联系
It's what we can all use to communicate.
在留言板上发布一个信息
Post a note on the message board.
叫什么?
What's it called?
Europeangoldfinch.net
Europeangoldfinch.Net.
那是一种鸟  对吧?
That's a bird, right?
我找到了
I got something.
是地窖的地基
It's the silo's foundation.
啊  太好了
Hells, yeah.
谢谢你  查尔斯
Thank you, Charles.
我们只要再找到地基的边缘
We just need to find the edge
然后挖到下面去
and dig underneath it.
我们就能拿到钱了...
We'll get the money...
然后就可以回家了
hit the back roads.
嗯...
Uh, well...
怎么了?
what's wrong?
我们要先到图勒镇停一下
We gots to stop in Tooele first
加点油
and gas up the ride.
我以为你已经加过了
I thought you already did that.
伙计  当时花店出了那事儿
Man, when the garden center thing happened
我就忘了  行了吧?
I just forgot, all right?
我要你回镇上去
I want you to go back into town--
我要你把车加满油
I want you to gas up that car.
因为我不想开车
Because I'm not driving
载着几百万钱到处逛  明白了吗?
around with millions of dollars in the trunk, do you understand?
伙计  为什么要我去做?
Man, why do I gots to do it...?
好吧
Okay.
最好去看看我们的朋友
Better check in on our friend.
...无时无刻
all the time.
金脚趾小姐
Miss tinsel toes.
比利?
Billy?
嗯
Yeah.
我给你做了个三明治
I made you a sandwich.
加了花生黄油和果酱还去掉了面包皮
Peanut butter and jelly with the crusts cut off.
就像你喜欢的
Just like you like.
我太高兴了你能回来
I'm so glad you came back.
我不想说我已经跟你说过了
I don't want to say I told you so,
但只是...
but that was
那女孩确实不适合你
just not the girl for you.
那是哪里?
Where is that?
什么哪里  宝贝
Where's what, sweetheart?
那幅画
That painting.
噢  那是荷兰
Oh, it's Holland.
我在那里长大  你知道的啊
Where I grew up.You know that.
真漂亮
It's beautiful.
噢  没有地方比那更美了
Oh, there's no place better.
那里很平静  远离尘嚣...
It's so peaceful, so...so protected from this crazy world
你好  接线员
Hello, operator?
有个闯进了我家...
There's an intruder in my house...
你好  太太?
hello, ma'am?
太太  你还在吗?
Ma'am? Are you there?
太太?
Hello, ma'am?
那有人吗?
Is anyone there?
听说今天在图勒镇有动静?
Heard you had some activity in Tooele today.
是有点状况
A bit.
看不出来哪里需要FBI亲自来一趟
Don't see how it warrants a visit from the FBI.
只是有辆被偷的车被扔在镇外  属于...
A stolen car was dumped just outside of town,
一个在圣路易斯学校上学的女生
belonging to a woman who went to school in ST. Louis,
我说得对吗?
am I getting that right?
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
然后这里
And then here,
老板的女朋友报告他失踪了
the owner's girlfriend reports him missing,
然后老板的朋友过来
看了看...然后他也不见了
by to check it out and he...goes missing, too.
是的  但伍迪和切特常丢下所有的事
Yeah, but Woody and Chet have been known to drop everything
去打野猪
and go boar hunting
当时候到了他们就会出现
when the opportunity presents itself,
他们不会告诉
and they don't tell
他们的老女人
their old ladies.
马宏先生我敢用我的午餐钱和你打赌
Mr. Mahone, I'll bet you my lunch money
这附近没什么不对劲
there's nothing amiss around here.
伍迪的父亲过会就会带着钥匙过来
But Woody's dad'll be showing up soon with the keys and...
到时你可以自己看看
you can look for yourself.
哇  哇  你做什么?
Whoa, whoa. What are you doing?!
马宏先生
Mr. Mahone.
他们在这里
They're here.
那些逃犯在镇上
Those escaped convicts.They're here in town.
谁在那里?
Who's there?
是警察  太太
It's the police, ma'am.
你没事吧?
You okay?
还好
Yes.
你能告诉我发生了什么事吗?
Can you tell me what happened?
刚才有个陌生人
There was this strange man.
我给他做了个花生酱三明治
I made him a peanut butter sandwich.
我以为他是比利
I thought he was Billy.
一旦孩子们睡着了
And once the kids went to sleep,
我们就去洗澡
we'd take a bath.
洗很长时间
A long...bath.
然后  我就坐在那里
And afterwards, I'd just sit there
看着她...
and watch her...
做日常保养  你知道的
do her routine, see.
抹润肤乳  梳头发
Rub her lotion on, comb her hair.
穿上她的睡衣
Dress up in her nighttime fineries.
喔  羡慕死我了
Oh, you're killing me.
她脖子很敏感...这里
she had this spot on her neck right...here.
次都能让她起疙瘩
Gave her goosebumps every time.
还有那香水...
and that perfume...
我的前夫
my ex.
他是一个会计师
He was an accountant.
他很不爱说话
He was really buttoned up.
他真该死  谢谢你  山姆
He was ram, damn, thank you, sam.
哎  他应该感到可耻
Well, shame on him.
为什么要结束
Why did it end
你和你所说的那个女人的关系?
with that lady　you were talking about?
只是选择了不同的道路
Just went out separate ways.
你想知道...
Do you know...
给一颗受伤的心最好的治疗办法 是什么吗?
what I think the best cure is　for a broken heart?
是什么?
Do tell.
回到属于你自己的位置
Get back on the bike.
不管它是什么样子
Whatever bike it is.
阿门
Amen to that.
说到...
Speaking of.
你能帮我个忙吗?
Could you do something for me?
当然可以
I'm certain of it.
过来
Come here.
只要你小心谨慎一点
Only you have to be very discreet.
他们不需要一起过来
They don't come any discreter.
你知道...那个高大的家伙
You know that, that big guy
强壮的家伙...那个...
the strong guy that, that doesn't...
不太爱说话的那个
speak much?
你能不能过去问问他
Would you go in there
他愿不愿意
and ask him
等他忙完  来和我喝杯酒?
if he would like to　have a drink with me after he punches out?
好吗
Please.
你刚才一直在耍我  是吗?
You've just been playing me this whole time,　haven't you?
拜托
Come on.
别这样嘛
Don't be like that.
你能不能进去问问你朋友?
Would you just go in and ask your friend?　Please?
嘿  爸爸
Hey, dad.
莎拉我一直试着联系你
Sara. I've been trying to reach you.
噢  知道
Uh, yeah.
我一直在开会
I've been meeting
一整天都在和我的辩护律师在一起
with　my defense attorneys all day.
嗯...你在华盛顿?
Um...you in Washington?
是的  但我下一班飞机就回来了
Yeah, but I'm coming back on the next flight.
我以为你要在那里待一阵子
I thought you were going to be there for a while.
不  不  计划改变了
No, no.　Plans changed, okay?
莎拉  你还记得那个人吗
Sara, do you remember that guy
我在你公寓见过的那个家伙?
that　I met with you in your apartment?
我要你离他远点
I want you to stay away from him.
谁  兰斯?和我一个组的?
Who, Lance?　From my, my group?
是的  是的  就是他
Yeah, yeah, that's him.
他并不像他自己所说的那样
He is not who he says he is.
我还发现了一些其他的事情
And I found out some other things, too.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
你是对的
You were right.
莎拉
Sara?
我得挂了
I gotta go.
嗯  先生  麻烦稍等一下
Uh, just one second, sir.Thank you.
我能为你做些什么?
How can I help you?
三号加40美元
Just put $40 on three.
抱歉  唔...
I'm sorry.Uh...
- 哪个泵?- 三号
- what pump was that?- Three.
噢  那个堵住了
Oh, that one's been sticking.
好  那我移一下车
Okay, well, then, I'll move the car.
噢  不  不...
Ah, no. Don't--
不麻烦你了  我叫...
don't trouble yourself.I'll have the
我叫技修工帮你加好了
mechanic come out and pump it for you.
嘿  我们有个顾客在三号等着!
Hey, we got a customer waiting on three!
嘿  伙计  我赶时间  快点好吗?
Yo, look, man, I'm in a hurry, all right?
噢  他马上就来
Oh, he'll be right out.
等会儿
Just one second.
把手放在头后然后跪下
Put your hands behind your head and drop to your knees.
跪下!
Drop!
他们在那里?
Where are they?
他们...在...那里?
Where...are...they?
哦  好吧
All right, man.
尽管只有一只手  我想他
One hand or not, I think
也应该来挖吧,你说呢?
hillbilly needs to be up ahead digging.What you think?
好样的
Good man.
哦
Oh
你见鬼的上来干什么?
What the hell are you doing up here?
唔  对不起  珍妮特
Uh, I'm sorry, Jeannette.
我在楼下没看到你
I just didn't see you downstairs.
我听到有声音
I heard something.
我为闯进来道歉
I apologize for barging in.
她对强壮高大的男人感兴趣
She's got the hots for the big, strong one.
对不起  珍妮特
I'm sorry, Jeannette.
我们正要...我们马上回去工作
We're gonna...we're gonna get back to work now.
不  我想你们做完了
No, I think y'all are done,
我想你们现在都需要离开
and I think y'all need to leave now.
我们快做完了
We're almost finished.
不  我认为你们做完了  好吗?
No, I think you are finished, okay?
而且我要你们现在就离开我家
And I want you to leave my house now.
苏克雷  出去看看
Sucre, check it out.
警察
Cop.
感谢上帝
thank god.
你想去那?
Where are you going?
放开她  帝博格
Let her go, T-Bag.
噢  上帝
oh, god.
她是我们离开的唯一出路  帅哥
She's our only way out of this, pretty.
闭上嘴  老骚货 否则我割断你的喉咙
Don't say a word, you old whore, or I'll cut your throat out.